paperbackswap.com 2019-12-14

# PaperBackSwap :: Privacy Policy

This page describes how PaperBackSwap handles information that we learn about consumers when consumers visit www.PaperBackSwap.com (aka "the Site"), or contact us by mail, phone, or email. Any personally identifying information you provide is voluntary. We use it to fulfill a request you make or to assist us in carrying out our mission: facilitating the trading of books, DVDs, music, or other media between our club members. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**   
PaperBackSwap does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated entities, except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

  1. We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, requests by law enforcement, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
  2. We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of PaperBackSwap's Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law.
  3. We may transfer information about you if PaperBackSwap is acquired by or merged with another company.

**Affiliated Entities**   
PaperBackSwap may engage in marketing products or services in cooperation with other companies. While engaged in a cooperative relationship with PaperBackSwap, such companies are considered affiliated entities and PaperBackSwap may share your information with them, including your name, address, email address, and other personal information that you have provided to us. If you purchase postage through the Site, the United States Postal Service and our postage partner, Endicia, require that we collect and share your personal information with Endicia and the United States Postal Service. Information sharing includes, but may not be limited to, your name, address, email address, credit card number, and telephone number and such additional information as may be requested or required to complete or facilitate a postage purchase transaction. Your information can then be used according to their respective privacy policies, which can be found at 

<https://www.endicia.com/PrivacyPolicy/>

and 

<https://about.usps.com/who-we-are/privacy-policy/welcome.htm>

**Posted Communications**   
PaperBackSwap may make message boards, opinion forums, bulletin board services or other interactive communication facilities available to users of the Site. Posted communications are publicly viewable and searchable through Google or other search engines. PaperBackSwap cannot review all communications made on or through the Site. PaperBackSwap reserves the right to use posted materials for its own purposes for marketing, communication, advertising, or any other purpose at the sole discretion of PaperBackSwap.

**If you visit our Web sites to browse, read, or download information:**   
We may collect and store: the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet; the Internet protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using; the browser software you use; your operating system and other information about the computer and programs that you use to access the Site; the date and time you access the Site; the pages that you visit within the Site; and the Internet address of the site from which you linked directly to the Site.

We use this information to determine the number of visitors to different sections of the Site, to ensure the Site is working properly, and to help us make the Site more useful. We also use it to track or record information about individuals and their accounts.

We also use "cookies" or tracking mechanisms that collect personally identifying information on the Site. A "cookie" is a small text file that a Web site can place on your computer's hard drive in order, for example, to collect information about your activities on the site or to make it possible for you to use an online "shopping cart" to keep track of items you wish to order. The cookie transmits this information back to PaperBackSwap's computer which, generally speaking, is the only computer that can read it. Many consumers do not know that "cookies" are being placed on their computers when they visit Web sites. If you want to know when this happens, or to prevent it from happening, you can set your browser to warn you when a Web site attempts to place a "cookie" on your computer. However, if you do this, PaperBackSwap will not recognize you when you visit, and you will not be able to order books or other media through our service. We require that cookies be enabled for you to participate as a member of this club. Of course, you may delete any cookies that the Site places on your hard drive after you place an order and simply register again on your next visit.

**If you become a club member:**   
We will request your name, address, email address, and other personally identifiable information. Once you register with PaperBackSwap and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous.

PaperBackSwap also collects information about your transactions with us and other club members, including a list of media that you have ordered. Except under a court order or other similar legally sufficient demand, we will not disclose your media choices to anyone or any nonaffiliated company.

PaperBackSwap uses the information you provide in order to fulfill your requests for media, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for our clients.

**How We Use and Disclose Information**   
If you choose to provide personally identifying information to us, we may use and disclose it as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Children**   
Children under 18 are not permitted to use the PaperBackSwap service. 

**Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**  
You can edit your PaperBackSwap Account Information at any time.

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the PaperBackSwap service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the PaperBackSwap Newsletter, that are considered part of your PaperBackSwap account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.

You can cancel your PaperBackSwap account at any time. Please read our Terms of Use for information about refunds and other account closing matters.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
PaperBackSwap reserves the right to make changes to this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your PaperBackSwap account or by placing a prominent notice on the Site.
